[Melody of Golden Age]
[Episode 33]
It's the first time
I've heard someone singing nursery rhymes in a graveyard.
On this dark and windy night,
it's quite intriguing.
Oh, it's you.
You're the one who saved me.
You can just treat me
as a mysterious person,
Ghost Face.
Or as a friend.
Secretary Lu,
you came to the Imperial Investigation Department,
and yet you're leaving
without even saying hello to me?
Lai Luozhi
did so many bad things.
That must have been a disguise.
Perhaps
his approach to me
was also part of some scheme.
Excuse me.
Make way, please.
Coming through!
Nerd Jiang!
Thank you, sir.
Here.
Have a taste.
Try it.
What are you up to?
Why are you following me?
To... To protect you.
Protect me?
How long have you been following me?
Not... Not long.
So this is why
recently, it's always been Yun Que
who's by Commander Xu's side.
It's because you've been spending
all your time following me, right?
Not entirely.
Yun Que...
You idiot.
That's your boss.
Why are you following me?
I'm worried you might encounter danger.
Then why didn't you just tell me?
Why act like a thief?
You wouldn't have agreed.
Sir.
How much?
I've already paid.
You
are still the same as when you were a child,
always eager to throw gold ingots around,
without considering if it's worth it.
Nonsense.
I, Lu Chuichui,
am always meticulous with money
and never spend recklessly.
How do you know things about my childhood?
You're blushing.
Why are you blushing?
You haven't even had any wontons.
Come with me.
This... This...
Such a huge gold ingot.
When did you
become so rich?
A man shouldn't spend
his whole life serving others.
You should do something more meaningful
and protect more people.
Lady Lu.
I'm yours from now on.
From now on,
I am yours.
It's you?
That poor boy who had to sell himself?
Chuichui.
I've listened to you.
I've tried my best to help
many, many, many people.
From the moment you gave me this gold ingot,
I, Jiang Langxing,
have been yours, Lu Chuichui.
Sister.
[Auspiciousness and Good Luck]
[Elegant Residence]
Grand Commander Shen.
I've heard that you've
never been fond of attending such banquets, Grand Commander Shen.
I didn't expect you
to bring Mrs. Shen along to my banquet today.
This truly delights me to no end.
Even Grand Commander Shen has arrived.
[Elegant Residence]
Why is Lord Lai, who's equal in fame to White Ghost,
still nowhere to be seen?
I, Lai, am late.
It looks like it's about to snow.
I wonder if my elder sister may have the honor
to join Princess Ying and the ladies
in admiring the snow together?
Sister.
I didn't expect
that you'd bring your esteemed sister here, Lord Lai.
It truly honors me.
I, Luofu, arrived late.
Please forgive me, everyone.
Why don't you all take a seat?
I will personally
pour wine for everyone as an apology.
Very well.
Please be seated.
[Wine]
Your Highness.
[Elegant Residence]
Apologies for my rudeness.
She looks so agile,
not at all like
someone who has been injured.
Could it be that in Gannan Area,
you really mistook someone else for her?
[Elegant Residence]
I've heard that you're not only pretty, but also very talented, Mrs. Shen.
Why don't you dance for us
to liven up the atmosphere?
That's indeed true.
It's rare for Mrs. Shen to attend a banquet like this.
So naturally, she should give Prince Xian some face.
I believe she's not become arrogant
just because she's now favored by
Her Majesty.
Don't you agree?
Yes. Indeed.
Minister Zhang.
[Elegant Residence]
I remember when you were petitioning for
the marriage between the Shen and Yan families in front of Her Majesty,
you said the Yan family had a daughter
who's skilled in writing, singing, calligraphy, and dancing,
with a reputation as a virtuous lady,
unmatched in Xiang'an.
We should indeed take this opportunity
to let everyone here
see her talent.
I have also heard
that Mrs. Shen once amazed the entire audience
with a pipa dance
at the Kaiyang Festival.
I wonder if you could
perform a new piece
here at my Mansion?
Dr. Yan must have taught his daughter
all six types of arts.
Why not entertain us all?
Today, my wife...
Honey.
Since you insist,
I, Yan Xing, shall entertain you all.
Honey,
may I borrow your sword?
Fortunately, I've been secretly observing
when Shen Du practices his swordsmanship every day.
Lord Lai.
Isn't your sister
supposed to be a sheltered lady?
How could she have
such formidable martial arts skills?
Her figure and technique...
Why does it look somewhat familiar?
It seems like
I've seen it somewhere before.
[Elegant Residence]
Sorry for having offended you.
Lord Lai.
Xing's swordsmanship is not refined,
and she accidentally offended your sister.
Fortunately, your sister
has profound martial arts skills.
She exchanged a few moves with me,
which I believe shouldn't be considered a disruption to the elegance of the banquet.
It's no matter.
Splendid.
Splendid indeed.
Mrs. Shen and
Lord Lai's sister's
swordplay was truly magnificent.
It was a feast for my eyes.
How disgraceful.
You'd better go back and tidy yourself up.
You were too bold just now.
But it worked, didn't it?
I believe you've found a definite answer to
the doubts in your heart, right?
The one I encountered in Gannan Area
was indeed Lai Luofu.
Honey.
It might look easy,
but the sword was so heavy to swing.
I almost
dropped it on the ground several times.
Mrs. Shen, you're pretty and talented,
and you share such a romantic relationship with Grand Commander Shen.
It's truly enviable.
The swordplay by Grand Commander and his wife
was indeed eye-opening.
However, the piece
Musician Jin just played...
seems unfamiliar to me.
I composed this new piece
to celebrate the Winter Solstice.
It's called "Joy and Sorrow."
Musician Jin
is Mother's favorite musician.
It's extremely difficult to hear him perform on ordinary days.
I didn't expect that on Prince Xian's banquet today,
[Elegant Residence]
not only did he managed to invite Musician Jin here
to perform for us,
but he'd also compose a new piece for us.
It's truly enviable.
I didn't expect that
we'd hear
Musician Jin's new composition at today's banquet, either.
It's indeed an unexpected pleasure.
The cold weather portends snow.
At such an elegant banquet,
ladies and gentlemen,
let's raise our glasses together
and thank Prince Xian for his invitation.
[Elegant Residence]
[Lai's Mansion]
Help me!
It hurts! It hurts so much!
Help me, please!
You were injured by Shen Du in Gannan Area.
I spent a fortune to find the miraculous medicine from the Western Regions
to temporarily suppress
your wounds,
allowing you to appear as if you were perfectly well
and attend the banquet to prove your innocence today.
But you recklessly showed your bravado
and exposed yourself!
Still not admitting your mistake?
I want to kill Shen Du!
You're now wounded on top of your previous injuries,
and you've aroused everyone's suspicions.
For now,
you can't show your face in public anymore.
No. No!
No.
Give me some time.
Give me a little more time.
I'll...
I'll recover in no time.
Recover?
And make others suspect
that you impersonated Chen Huo'e again?
Trust me.
I'm still useful.
I'm still of use.
I still need to play the role
of your elder sister, right?
Give me some time.
Trust me.
I'll recover.
I'll be obedient.
Help me!
I'm still useful!
Help me, please.
It hurts so much!
Please help me!
Today is the Winter Solstice, but it hasn't snowed.
Are you planning
to turn yourself into a snowman?
I plan to make dumplings for you.
Making dumplings. Look.
Madam.
The palace eunuchs are here again.
The Grand Empress Dowager has summoned you.
Now you're going to the palace
even more often than I do.
Got it.
I'll go get changed right away.
I'll finish cooking them for you after I return.
I'm off.
Your Majesty, this humble servant pays respects to you.
You may rise.
Come closer,
Ms. Yan.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
It's the Winter Solstice today.
I've let all others go celebrate the festival
and only snatched you to keep me company.
Mr. Shen won't blame me, will he?
You must be joking, Your Majesty.
Come here.
Sit down.
I heard that
yesterday, Mr. Lai
also played a joke
on Mr. Shen, didn't he?
Yes.
The two of them
are my right-hand men.
You should advise Mr. Shen
not to have any misunderstandings
with Lai Luozhi.
It would be best if the matter ends here.
I'm grateful for the your concern, Your Majesty.
Although I don't know the details,
my husband
has been serving you
wholeheartedly, Your Majesty.
Surely, he won't harbor
any biased or selfish thoughts.
It's about time for snow.
The year-end is approaching,
and I've aged another year.
May you live for thousands of years, Your Majesty.
That's not necessary.
Sit down. Sit down.
Today,
there's no one else in the palace.
There's no need to be so formal.
I am just
a mortal being.
How could I live for thousands of years?
They respect me,
and fear me even more.
Because in this vast palace,
there is no one
who can stand shoulder to shoulder with me.
I see that Lord Baohuan
and Madam Xu
both treat you with utmost respect, Your Majesty.
That's because of the favor I've granted them.
You still have
Princess Yong'an
and Prince Xian, Your Majesty.
They are both
your children, Your Majesty.
They
are only eagerly eyeing
the position beside Qi,
that future position of Regent.
They're hoping for me to age quickly,
so they can grasp power.
How could they still remember
their duties as children?
Alright.
Let's not talk about them.
I summoned you here today
because I heard
how protective Mr. Shen is of you.
It suddenly reminded me of my days with the late emperor.
He was also protective of me like that.
He was always a person
who'd avoid conflicts with others,
but for my sake,
he would stand against the entire court.
I'm truly getting old.
Old indeed.
Lately,
I've been really fond of reminiscing.
Yan Xing.
Mr. Shen's love for you
is pure and genuine.
It even makes my previous arrangement of your marriage
seem a bit insensitive.
You're too kind, Your Majesty.
In Shen Du's heart,
you hold a very important place.
It's exactly because of this that
I want to advise you
not to let dark clouds obscure your judgment.
No matter the time or circumstances,
cherish your loved one.
I'll bear it in mind, Your Majesty.
[Shen's Mansion]
Si.
Master asked you
to return to the Yan's Mansion immediately.
Father?
Now?
Yes.
Please get in the carriage.
[Shen's Mansion]
Xing.
Come here, come here.
Minister Zhang has a few questions for you.
You two talk.
Minister Zhang.
We just met yesterday
at the banquet in Prince Xian's Mansion.
May I ask why you
have specially come to the Yan's Mansion
to see me today?
I heard that you've been
repeatedly summoned to the palace lately, Xing.
You seem to be in high favor with Her Majesty.
Minister Zhang, you flatter me.
The Grand Empress Dowager
just wanted to
have some casual conversation with me.
To be able to have casual conversations with the Grand Empress Dowager
is a blessing that many people
couldn't achieve in several lifetimes.
You've been by Shen Du's side
through life and death,
and now you've gained the Grand Empress Dowager's favor.
It's truly remarkable.
Now that you're riding high on success, Xing,
do you still remember
why you were arranged to marry Shen Du?
Today is the Winter Solstice.
I won't beat around the bush with you.
Just tell me what
the Grand Empress Dowager discussed with you,
and what has happened
in the Shen family recently.
Tell me everything in detail.
I don't know anything, Your Excellency.
Are you trying to rebel?
Minister Zhang, you've been using my father and the Yan family
to control me for a long time.
I did indeed marry into the Shen family
in place of my third sister, Caiwei.
However, I
have been solely focused on handling cases in the Ministry of Justice
and easing the burdens of the Grand Empress Dowager.
I know nothing else,
and I cannot know anything else.
I beg for your mercy, Minister Zhang.
Xing.
Do you think that having gained
the favor of the Grand Empress Dowager and Shen Du,
you can act with impunity?
Do you think I can no longer
control you
and the Yan family?
Royal favor can change in an instant,
and Shen Du can barely protect himself.
Yet you believe he can protect you
and your Yan family?
I don't want to rely on anyone.
I only want to rely on myself.
Good.
You've grown bold,
haven't you?
This time,
I accompanied my husband
to Gannan Area
to investigate the Half-faced Ghosts
and the Fire Moth Sect along the way.
We gained many insights about the frontier,
and we also uncovered
many unexpected stories
by following the clues.
I wonder if you'd be
interested in hearing about it, Minister Zhang?
What do you want to say?
Yan Xing.
Don't you spread baseless rumors.
Since you don't want to hear it, Minister Zhang,
I won't speak of it.
However, during my review
of the Ministry of Justice's files today,
a question arose in my mind.
Regarding the old case of the Shen family,
why didn't you submit a single memorial
and take no stance on such a major case, Minister Zhang?
Publicly,
you were already a pillar of the court at that time.
Privately,
weren't you
a classmate of Lord Shen Bingzhu, Minister Zhang?
What are you implying?
What exactly do you know?
I don't know anything specific,
nor do I know what I should know.
You have no evidence,
yet you're trying to threaten me?
If you have any questions, Minister Zhang,
just come to the Shen's Mansion and ask me directly.
Coming out of your way
to the Yan's Mansion to trouble my wife
is quite inappropriate, isn't it?
I originally thought
that you were an upright official in the court, Minister Zhang,
above the dirty dealings of officialdom.
But now, how have you stooped to
threatening a woman?
Goodbye.
Xing.
Mother.
Caiwei, Yijiao, Mojie.
Why are you all out here?
Here.
That old fool, your father.
He's spineless
and only knows how to harm his daughter.
You came back on the Winter Solstice,
yet you left without even having a meal.
I know
you must feel wronged inside.
Right.
Mother and Ms. Jin made glutinous rice and date cakes and dumplings
for you and Brother-in-law.
They'd been waiting for you to come back
and reheated them several times already.
Then they heard you had left.
Ms. Jin got so anxious that she almost cried.
Mother.
I'm sorry.
Why should you apologize?
It's all your father's fault.
Haven't you always
loved eating this since you were little?
Eat up, Xing.
It's still warm.
Thank you, Yijiao.
Thank you, Mojie.
Xing.
How have you been at the Shen's Mansion lately?
Everything's been good.
That's good.
The other day, I heard Father,
Mo Jie and Shiyuan talking.
I heard that the Grand Empress Dowager
favored Lai Luozhi
and suppressed Grand Commander Shen,
but to maintain a balance, seemingly,
she's been summoning you to the palace daily to accompany her.
It's not that serious.
Xing.
Like I said before,
if you and that White Ghost
could live harmoniously as husband and wife
and live happily together,
of course that would be good.
But if you had to live
with your neck on the knife's edge every day,
constantly worrying all the time,
then you might as well come home.
No matter what,
there's always a place for you at the Yan's Mansion.
That's right.
Ms. Jin might have been a bit blunt,
but it's all for your own good.
No matter what,
your happiness is the most important thing.
Please don't make any more sacrifices
for the Yan family.
Thank you, Mother,
and brothers and sisters
for your concern.
I'm doing well now.
Really well.
Then we can rest assured.
Oh, right.
Today is the Winter Solstice holiday.
It's rare for us to have some time off.
Why don't we
go take a stroll in the streets together?
He doesn't eat people.
Then let's... Go?
Your family members all care for you very much.
The Yan household is peaceful.
Although there are occasional disputes,
most of them come from good intentions.
I wonder
if this is my father's blessing
or
the blessing of us siblings.
It's my blessing.
My parents passed away early.
What I envy most
is a complete family.
Actually, since the first time
I went to the Yan's Mansion, I've been wondering
why you would aspire
to clear the wronged of the world.
It turns out you've been happy and healthy since childhood,
with a pure sense of justice in your heart,
without a trace of impurity.
From now on,
they will all be your family.
Honey.
Be careful.
I didn't expect the Grand Commander who strikes fear into everyone's hearts
to be so tender-hearted
in front of his beloved wife.
Why are you here with
a constable?
Yan Xing.
Don't you know that Lu Chuichui
is going to marry
one of our constables?
Don't talk nonsense.
You and Jiang Langxing...
You two are a couple now?
Go ahead and laugh at me all you want.
Why would I laugh at you?
I'm happy for you.
You've finally come to your senses.
How did you discover
that Jiang Langxing had feelings for you?
I...
What was the reason?
Of course it's because
you're beautiful and kind-hearted,
and exceptionally intelligent.
Oh, you're blushing.
I also wanted to ask you
when you plan to hold the wedding banquet.
I want to get married on the same day as you.
You're getting married too?
Who are you marrying?
Yan Xing.
Have you gone silly
from investigating the cases?
Can't you see?
Of course, I'm marrying Commander Xu.
Congratulations.
Thanks a lot.
Shen Du.
I'm already over you.
So, from now on,
you must treat Xing well.
If you scare Xing away,
I'm afraid no other woman in this world will like you.
Then you won't be able to find another wife.
So what?
In this life,
I'm content with only having Yan Xing as my wife.